<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://paurubiella.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://paurubiella.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2024-03-09T22:42:16+00:00</updated><id>https://paurubiella.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Why am I doing this?</title><link href="https://paurubiella.com/blog/2024/why-am-i-doing-this/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why am I doing this?"/><published>2024-03-07T12:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-03-07T12:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://paurubiella.com/blog/2024/why-am-i-doing-this</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://paurubiella.com/blog/2024/why-am-i-doing-this/"><![CDATA[<p>The truth is, I don’t know where to start.</p> <p>I’m Pau, a developer just like any other, who, taking advantage of the holidays, has decided to set up this site.</p> <p>Why? Well, because for years I’ve had the domain but I’ve used it privately to access my resources or run tests, but I thought, why not create a small site to share my knowledge, experiments, and adventures with other people?</p> <p>The idea of this site, apart from giving me a bit more visibility, is to have a place where I can share my knowledge, since as a hobby, I usually experiment with new technologies, whether it’s IoT, 3D printing, or just programming.</p> <p>Currently, I’m in the process of automating my home. Going into a bit of detail, I already have blinds, heating, and some lights (the ones I usually leave on). All of this is centralized using HomeAssistant software.</p> <p>I’m also quite a fan of 3D printing. Being able to create the piece you need for a specific purpose is amazing to me, and being able to do it at home is even better. I have a modified Ender3Pro printer, where I’ve installed the extruder from the Ender3s1Pro, as well as its motherboard, along with a dual Z-axis and Klipper installed on a Raspberry Pi (powered by the printer itself).</p> <p>Of course, it goes without saying that the printer itself can be turned on and off using HomeAssistant and can be managed using the printer’s own web interface panel.</p> <p>I’m also interested in topics such as security, networking, infrastructure like Docker or Kubernetes, etc.</p> <p>I think this gives you an idea of how curious I am, and you also know a bit more about me and what interests me.</p> <p>I hope the site is useful for you.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="personal"/><category term="personal"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[First post]]></summary></entry></feed>